rocketreach.co 2018-10-29

# RocketReach's Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Welcome! This page describes RocketReach’s practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of the information we collect from and about you when you use our Service. We take our obligations regarding your privacy seriously and have made every effort to draft this Privacy Policy in a manner that is clear and easy for you to understand.

This policy applies to information we collect on this website, as well from email, text, or other electronic messages exchanged between you and this website. It also applies to data collected through your use of any RocketReach or third party advertisement or application if that advertisement or application includes a link to this Privacy Policy. 

## What information do we collect?

We collect personal information, such as your name and email address, when you register for an account on the Service.

If you are a user of our paid premium service, we will utilize a third party credit card payment processing company to collect payment information, including your credit card number, billing address and billing email. This information is collected by the third party processing company, as disclosed in our Terms of Purchase. We do not store your payment information. 

As you use our Services, we may use "cookies" and similar technologies to collect and store information that is generated automatically as you use the Services. This information is collected to help us understand your preferences, both individually and in aggregate, so that we can offer a better user experience. Most browsers allow you to manage cookies including blocking and deleting them. If you block or delete our cookies, the Services may not work at all for you. We may also use trusted third party services to track this information on our behalf, such as Google Analytics. Note, cookies do not contain personal data. 

## When do we collect information?

We collect personal information for the purpose it is voluntarily submitted and only at the time it is needed to fulfill that purpose.

We collect information that you voluntarily submit you when you register on our site, use service features, or pay for premium services. In addition, we collect anonymous usage data via cookies and pixels to help us remember your preferences and optimize user experience for you and other users of the site. 

## How do we use your information? 

We will not use you information to contact you unless we are responding to a contact initiated by you or for one of the following reasons: 

  * Managing your access to service
  * Sending you information on how to access features or updates
  * Fulfilling requests made by you

Your account information is completely segregated from the product parts of the Service and will not be used for any purpose other than to enable management and use of your account and the Services. 

## How do we protect your information?

The security of your information is important to us. We employ physical, technical, or managerial safeguards to protect your data. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) as part of our service, we encrypt the transmission of that information using industry-standard encryption. All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website as the device use to access RocketReach, services you use to access the website, or 3rd parties may be compromised. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

The website may contain links or information to other websites, which are provided for your convenience only. RocketReach accepts no responsibility for the integrity of third-party links, the linked content, or your use of the links or the linked content. Access to linked websites is entirely at your own risk, and you should consult the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy of any third-party site before using their information or providing information to them. 

## Third Party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information for marketing purposes without your consent.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

## Children

Our Services are not intended for children under 16 years of age. No one under age 16 may provide any information to us via our website or any other means. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us at support@rocketreach.co. If RocketReach becomes aware that information has been collected from a child under 16 years of age, we will take prompt action to ensure deletion of that information.

## Email

We are CAN-SPAM Act compliant, we collect your email address in order to: 

  * Process orders and subscriptions and to send information and updates pertaining to orders and subscriptions 
  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.

## Dispute Resolution

Any questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of personal information should be directed to RocketReach at the postal or email address provided below. We will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of personal information in accordance with the principles contained in this Policy. For complaints that cannot be resolved between RocketReach and the complainant, RocketReach agrees to participate in dispute resolution procedures as required by US and EU data protection laws.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

This Policy may be amended from time to time, consistent with the requirements of the US and EU data protection laws. It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at:   
RocketReach  
41 Royal Oak Ct.  
Mountain View, CA 94040  
privacy@rocketreach.co   
Last Edited on 2018-06-17
